gnld.com 2011-11-11

# GNLD: A Better Way of Life

GNLD recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy and security of information we may collect from you. The purpose of this policy is to inform you of how we handle information we may learn about you from your visit to our website.

**Use and Collection of Information**  
When visiting the GNLD website you may be asked for certain types of personally identifiable information. We receive and store information you give us through the website or in any other manner. We use such information including name, electronic or physical mailing address, telephone numbers, Tax Identification Numbers (TINs) and credit card numbers for a variety of purposes including: 

  * Processing Distributor Applications
  * Confirmation and fulfillment of orders
  * Communication of corporate events or policies
  * Compliance with applicable laws and requirements
  * User feed-back and survey responses to improve GNLD Service

**Financial and Tax Information:**  
Financial information, including account numbers and credit card numbers are EXCLUSIVELY used for billing purposes, while TINs and Social Security Numbers are EXCLUSIVELY used for state and federal tax purposes. GNLD utilizes security measures to safeguard this private information.

**Third Parties**  
We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may share such information as necessary with the following third parties:

  * Any consultant/agent appointed by GNLD to plan, provide and/or administer distributor benefits.
  * Any employee of GNLD and its local and foreign affiliated/associated companies who have a need to access your personal information in order to carry out their responsibilities.
  * Any government agency or governmental, police or regulatory authority in order to meet legal security and regulatory requirements 
  * Up-line sponsoring Distributors with a need to know your status, progress and involvement.  

**Transfer  
**The consent you have provided to GNLD or its affiliates to use your personal information shall also extend to any person or corporation to which GNLD may transfer its business, provided that such information is used for the same purposes.

**Online Surveys**  
In the event that GNLD conducts online surveys, we may ask you to voluntarily provide demographic information. All responses are used exclusively for internal marketing and statistical purposes and are kept confidential.

**Website Links**  
GNLD may provide links to other websites that we believe are useful. Though we believe these sites meet our high standards, GNLD is not responsible for the content, actions or policies of third party websites. Additionally, GNLD is not responsible for the privacy notices or practices of such websites. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on computer hard drives. We may use cookies to recognize you when you return to the GNLD website in order to provide you with a better user experience. Our cookies do not contain any personal information such as social security or credit card numbers. GNLD’s use of Cookies allows you to use password-protected services in a single session without having to re-enter your password and to track your shopping cart status. GNLD’s use of Cookies also includes determination of which areas of our site are popular and to determine which region, content and language are appropriate.

**Security**  
GNLD has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information you provide. When you place an order or give GNLD personal information you are automatically on our secure server. 

**Access to Personal Information**  
You have the right to request and obtain the personal information GNLD has on file about you. You may request a correction of any data that is inaccurate. You may also request GNLD to inform you of the type of personal information maintained by GNLD Corporation. All requests must be in writing and should be addressed to:

GNLD Headquarters  
P.O. Box 5012  
Fremont, CA 94537-5012
